(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-17T01:27:25.075744",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
止まらない
Unstoppable
恋の罠に 囚われ 夢中に
Caught in the trap of love, totally obsessed!
よそ見ダーリン ダメダメよ
Don't you dare look away, darling!
痛いの飛んでけ 残るのは愛だけ
Fly away, pain, leaving only love behind!
キュンと 私の恋心
A sudden twinge of my loving heart!
一人は嫌い 触れるだけで
I hate being alone, just touching you
繋がるような 好きな感じじゃん
feels like we're connected, isn't that nice?
周りの嫌な意見 関係ない
I don't care what anyone else says around us,
いわゆるあの盲目なの
we're in that so-called blind love.
最高なファッションセンス 私になれない
That ultimate fashion sense I could never pull off—
うらやましい？ 悲しい？この話
are you envious? Sad? What is this story?
メンションで伝える気持ち
Feelings conveyed through mentions,
ほら言葉で伝えてほしいの
come on, I want you to tell me in words.
止まらない
Unstoppable
恋の罠に 囚われ 夢中に
Caught in the trap of love, totally obsessed!
よそ見ダーリン ダメダメよ
Don't you dare look away, darling!
痛いの飛んでけ 残るのは愛だけ
Fly away, pain, leaving only love behind!
これも辛いけど
Even though this is painful too,
騙して夢々におぼれ
deceive me and drown in dreams,
もう等身大の愛はないよ
there's no such thing as realistic love anymore.
恋の罠に 囚われ 夢中に
Caught in the trap of love, totally obsessed!
キュンと 私の恋心
A sudden twinge of my loving heart!
私たちは 指を交され
We locked our fingers together,
触れる時が 恋いすじゃんく
the moment we touch is a foolish junk.
あなたは今 誰のために
Who are you speaking of love to right now?
愛を語る？ 私でしょ？
It's me, right?
天才なファッションセンス
A genius fashion sense,
おとなじゃのりよ
ride it like an adult,
えなんとろねに ストロング 取り込んだりよ
attach a strong-arm...
ジャンキーなんせ 好きやのメロディ
Junkie, after all, I love this melody.
その心は 心臓から
That heart comes straight from my chest.
縛りたいの お互いに
I want to tie each other down,
挟まないと不意に 形にしなきゃ ダメダメよ
if we don't shape it suddenly, no way!
二人は従順に 若さは牢獄に
We are obedient, youth is in a prison,
乙女倍々で行こう
let's go with maiden double speed!
満たして 辛い 辛いの世界
Fulfilling, painful, painful world,
もう何千回と耐えた夜へ
toward the nights I endured thousands of times.
愛はお互いに 分からず夢中に
Love is mutual, lost in a trance,
きっと涙の アイワナムチュー
surely with tears, I wanna chu!
愛されたくて愛されたいの
Wanting to be loved, wanting to be loved,
やっぱりどうにか愛されたいよ
after all I somehow want to be loved.
人ってそういうもんじゃないの
Aren't people just like that?
曖昧みーまいん やばいねっじこ
Ambiguous, my mine, dangerous, stuck in gear,
説教はノー
lectures are a no!
止まらない恋の罠に 取りこまれ夢中に
Caught in the trap of unstoppable love, lost in a dream,
よそ見ダーリン ダメダメよ
looking away, darling, no way!
痛いの飛んでけ 残りの愛だけ
Fly away the pain, only the remaining love,
これも辛いけど
this is also painful, but
騙して 夢 夢に溺れ
deceive me, dreams, drown in dreams,
もう等身大の 愛はないよ
there is no longer life-sized love.
恋の罠に 取りこまれ夢中に
Caught in the trap of love, lost in a dream,
キュンとあたしの 恋心
my heart beats with a thump, my romantic heart.
ラララララ 病的アイニージェー
Lalalalala, pathological I-need-you,
ラララララ 孤独は病
lalalalala, loneliness is a disease,
ラララララ 盲目アイニージェー
lalalalala, blind I-need-you,
ずっとあなたに アイワナムチュー
forever I wanna chu with you!
思い出すのは君の歌 会話よりも鮮明だ
What I remember is your song, clearer than conversation.
どこへ行ってしまったのか いつも探すんだよ
Where did you go? I'm always searching for it.
思い出すのは君の歌 歌い笑う顔が鮮明だ
What I remember is your song, your singing, smiling face clear.
君に似合うんだよ ずっと見ていたいよ
It suits you so well, I want to watch you forever.
でも最後に見たいのは きっともう君の夢の中
But what I want to see at the very end is surely in your dreams.
もう一度 また聞かせてくれないか 聞きたいんだ
Won't you let me hear it once more? I want to hear it.
もっと騒げ怪獣の歌 まだ消えない 夢の歌歌えて
Roar more, monster's song, sing the song of dreams that still won't fade,
君がいつでも歌う怪獣の歌 まだ消えない 口ずさんでしまうよ
the monster's song you always sing, I still end up humming it.
もっと騒げ怪獣の歌 まだ消えない 夢の歌歌えて
Roar more, monster's song, sing the song of dreams that still won't fade,
君がいつでも歌う怪獣の歌 まだ消えない 口ずさんでしまうよ
the monster's song you always sing, I still end up humming it.
思い出すのは君がいた ギター持ってる君がいた
What I remember is you being there, you holding a guitar.
忘れられないんだよ だから僕が歌うよ
I can't forget it, that's why I'll sing.
でも最後に見たいのは きっともう君の夢の中
But what I want to see at the very end is surely in your dreams.
もう一度 また聞かせてくれないか 聞きたいんだ
Won't you let me hear it once more? I want to hear it.
もっと騒げ怪獣の歌 まだ消えない 夢の歌歌えて
Roar more, monster's song, sing the song of dreams that still won't fade,
君がいつでも歌う怪獣の歌 まだ消えない 口ずさんでしまうよ
the monster's song you always sing, I still end up humming it.
落ちてく過去は鮮明で 見せたい未来は繊細で
The falling past is vivid, the future I want to show is delicate,
過ぎてく日々に鈍感な君へ
to you who are insensitive to the passing days.
落ちてく過去は鮮明で 見せたい未来は繊細で
The falling past is vivid, the future I want to show is delicate,
過ぎてく日々に鈍感な君へ
to you who are insensitive to the passing days.
落ちてく過去は鮮明で 見せたい未来は繊細で
The falling past is vivid, the future I want to show is delicate,
過ぎてく日々に鈍感な君へ
to you who are insensitive to the passing days.
もっと騒げ怪獣の歌 まだ消えない 夢の歌歌えて
Roar more, monster's song, sing the song of dreams that still won't fade,
君がいつでも歌う怪獣の歌 まだ消えない 口ずさんでしまうよ
the monster's song you always sing, I still end up humming it.
The monster's song you always sing, I still end up humming it.
眠れない夜に 手を伸ばして 眠らない夜も また伸ばして
Reaching out on sleepless nights, reaching out once more on sleepless nights.
眠れない夜に手を伸ばして
Reaching out on a sleepless night,
眠れない夜をまた伸ばして
stretching out another sleepless night,
眠くないまだね
Still not sleepy yet,
そんな日々でいたいのにな
I wish I could stay in days like that.
眠れない夜に手を伸ばして
Reaching out on a sleepless night,
眠れない夜をまた伸ばして
stretching out another sleepless night,
眠くないまだね
Still not sleepy yet,
そんな夜に歌う　怪獣の歌
Singing on such a night, the monster's song.
落ちていく過去は鮮明で
The falling past is vivid,
見せたい未来は繊細で
the future I want to show is delicate,
過ぎてく日々に飢餓感な君へ
to you who feel starved by passing days.
今宵も頭上では
Tonight, high above,
綺麗な満月がキラキラ
a beautiful full moon sparkles.
幸せそうに世界を照らしている
Happily illuminating the world.
当時の私は
Back then, I
できそこないでどうしようもなくて
was good for nothing and helpless,
夜明け夢見ては地べた這いずり回っている
dreaming of dawn while crawling on the ground.
それでも誰かに見つけて欲しくて
Yet, wanting someone to find me,
夜空見上げて叫んでいる
I look up at the night sky and scream.
逃げ出したいが逃げ出せない
I want to run away, but I can't.
明るい未来は見えないね
I can't see a bright future.
それでもあなたに見つけて欲しくて
Still, wanting you to find me,
蝶のように舞い上がるの
I soar upward like a butterfly.
欠けた翼で飛んだ醜い星の子ミカヅキ
Mikazuki, the child of an ugly star who flew with chipped wings.
今宵も頭上では
Tonight, high above,
綺麗な満月がゆらゆら
a beautiful full moon sways.
誰かの腕に流されて
Swept away in someone's arms,
眠っている
I am sleeping.
当時の私は
Back then, I
ひとりの夜に押し潰されては
was crushed by a lonely night,
誰にも見えない闇這いずり回っている
crawling around in a darkness no one can see.
それでも誰にも負けたくなくて
Still, not wanting to lose to anyone,
宇宙の隅でもがいている
I'm struggling in the corner of the universe.
追い付きたいや、追い越したい
I want to catch up, I want to overtake,
夢見たような世界ね
in a world like a dream.
それでも誰かと比べてばかり
Still, always comparing myself to others,
周りを見ては立ち止まってかけ
stopping in my tracks as I look around,
欠けたものを探した
I searched for what was missing.
そんな自分を変えたい
I want to change myself like that.
それでもあなたと同じ景色が
Still, wanting to see the same scenery
また見たいから
with you once more,
泣き出したくても投げ出したくても
even when I want to cry or give up,
諦めたりはできない
I can't just give up.
それでもあなたに見つかるように
So that you can find me,
サナギは強く手を伸ばすの
the chrysalis strongly reaches out its hand.
欠けたもの抱きしめて願いを放つよミカヅキ
Embracing the missing piece, I release my wish, Mikazuki.
それでも誰かに見つけて欲しくて
Still, wanting someone to find me,
夜空見上げて叫んでいる
I look up at the night sky and scream.
泣き出したいけど泣き出せない
I want to start crying, but I can't.
もう後戻りなどできないね
I can't turn back anymore.
それでもあなたに見つけて欲しくて
Still, wanting you to find me,
蝶のように舞い上がるの
I soar upward like a butterfly.
欠けた翼で飛ぶよ
I'll fly with chipped wings.
醜い星の子ミカヅキ
Mikazuki, the child of an ugly star.
光を放ったミカヅキ
Mikazuki that radiated light.
今宵も頭上では
Tonight, high above,
綺麗な満月がキラキラ
a beautiful full moon sparkles.
今宵も頭上では 綺麗な満月がキラキラ
Evening overhead, the beautiful full moon is glittering
幸せそうに世界を照らしている
Illuminating the world happily
はい！愛はなぶつ怪獣の歌「ミカヅキ」でした！イェイ！
Hi! That was the song "Mikazuki"! Yay!
みんな見てる？ちゃんと見てた？
Did everyone watch? Did you watch properly?
3曲ね、連続で最初から歌っちゃいましたけど、どうでしたか？可愛かった？
I sang three songs in a row from the start, how was it? Was it cute?
ねえ、見て！ステージすごいの！見て、これ！
Hey, look! The stage is amazing! Look at this!
すごいでしょう？超かわいいよ！ほら、上とかさ
Isn't it amazing? Super cute! Look, up top and stuff
お月様があって、しよっこもいて、カメラマンやってくれてんだよね、上に、3人。見て！
There's a moon, and Shiyokko is there acting as cameraman up top, three of them. Look!
見えるかな？あいつ、あいつら
Can you see them? Those guys, those guys.
あ、照明らしい！照明らしい！かわい、え、かわいい！めちゃかわいいじゃん！
Ah, they're lighting! Lighting! Cute, eh, cute! They're super cute!
しよっこもね、帽子かぶっててめちゃかわいいんだよね。ここにいるけど。何持ってんだろね？
Shiyokko is wearing a hat too, super cute. They're right here. What are they holding?
ツッパリ棒みたいなの持ってう (笑)
They're holding something like a telescoping rod (laughs).
でね、で、見て見て！こっち！わあ、見て！こいつ超可愛い！
And, look look! Over here! Wow, look! This guy is super cute!
あ、いいじゃんこれ。ちょっと写真撮ってください。(笑) え、可愛いでしょう！
Ah, this is nice. Please take a picture. (Laughs) Eh, isn't it cute!
これはねメイド衣装のここに付いてるあの、ぬいぐるみだね。目玉の、目玉がボタンのぬいぐるみね (笑)
This is the stuffed toy attached to the maid outfit here. The eyeball stuffed toy with eyeball buttons (laughs).
いや、超可愛いんだよ！下はね、魔法陣になってんだよね。
Man, it's super cute! Down below, it's a magic circle.
いや、可愛すぎる本当に！めちゃピンクと紫で超可愛い！
Man, it's too cute, really! Super pink and purple, super cute!
ということで、新しいステージでした！可愛いでしょう！めっちゃしょんぽくって超可愛いよね！
So, that was the new stage! Isn't it cute? Super shonpoku and super cute!
で、あとね、後ろの、えー！
And also, the back, eh!
これが今回のサムネイルのイラストなんだけど、あれ？なんか…
This is the thumbnail illustration for this time, but huh? Somehow...
これ、誰だろ？ (笑) え、誰だろ誰だろ？
Who is this? (Laughs) Eh, who is it, who is it?
え、もしかして出てくるのかな、この先？え、どうなんだろう？
Eh, are they going to appear from now on? Eh, I wonder?
いや、わかんないな、わかんないんだけど、かもしれないよね？(笑) かもしれないんだよね！これも超可愛いし、これもサムネイルなんだけどね。
Well, I don't know, I don't know, but maybe, right? (Laughs) Maybe! This is super cute too, this is also a thumbnail.
ということで、なんと気づけばもう5年も経ってしまっていました！怖すぎる！
So, before I knew it, 5 whole years have already passed! Too scary!
まだ気分は新人バーチャルユーチューバーなのに (笑) 怖すぎるよ！はあ…
Even though I still feel like a rookie Virtual YouTuber (laughs) It's too scary! Ha...
5年目も頑張るぞ！ということで、あ…
I'll do my best in my 5th year too! So, ah...
明日は、紫咲シオン5周年記念でみんなたくさん可愛い写真撮ってツイートしてください！あとで見るよ！
Tomorrow is Murasaki Shion's 5th anniversary, everyone please take lots of cute photos and tweet them! I'll check them later!
はい！というわけで、ここからはゲストパートです！最後までたっぷりあるのでぜひ見てってください！最後まで見てね！頑張るぞー！
Yes! So, from here on is the guest part! There's plenty until the end, so please be sure to check it out! Watch till the end! Let's do our best!
劣等上等 BRING IT ON
Bring it on, inferior superiority
列島上々 不眠日和
Top of the archipelago, sleepless Japan
子供騙しのマスメティカ
Children's trick mathematics
バレてんだってそんなのってプライドがない
Being exposed, like that, there's no pride
レトちょっと BRING IT ON
Letty & Towa, BRING IT ON
レトちょっとお耳にバーク
Letty & Towa in your ears
子供でも死のままで狭いから
Even as kids, staying dead is too narrow
ご立派景勝 気取りで
Acting all high and mighty with a warning bell
世界の見聞物ばっかり一寸満点
Just watching world sights, hundred points
ほらもっと 間違って上等
Hey, bring it on, making mistakes is fine
退屈に手をかけて
Put your hands on the boredom
ママ やっぱあたしは こんなところじゃ終れない
Mama, I know I still can't end up in a place like this
ぬるくて気が触れそう ここ遊びも芝居もさようなら
It's so lukewarm I'm going crazy, goodbye to playing pretend
ずっとこのまになんてさあ 要らないよ
Being stuck like this forever, I don't need it
ダッダッダ 私 大人になる
Dadada, I'm becoming an adult
酸いも甘いも噛み分けて今
Tasting both the sweet and the sour now
パッパッパ 変わる時代
Papapa, a changing era
悪いことばかりじゃないでしょう
It's not all bad things, right?
過去も、
The past,
罪も、
the sins,
罰も、
the punishments,
すべて、
all of it
素手で、
with bare hands,
愛で、
with love,
生き抜いてやり返すわ
I'll survive and get back at you
Yeah ちょーはつ あたし達はno doubt
Yeah, provocation, we have no doubt
緑のあいつにばっか構ってんね
You're only paying attention to that green guy
"Are you free tonight?"
Called from you, now
お気に入りムスクと甘々な秘密纏う
I've been waiting…
I've been waiting...
This weekend night!!
今夜モノになるあたしのなにもかもが
溢れ出てるリビドーは好きその衝動
そんななら見ててよ伝家の宝刀いこう王道
「Haa… Chotto yocchatta kamo♥」
すべて見抜いて
余裕なんて見せないで
すべて見透かして
好きにさせて
ねえ早く連れていって
まつげすら触れちゃいそうな距離で
思考すら奪って探り当てて
その場のしぎ以上の余計なこと言っちゃいそうだな
吐息漏れるその唇をキスで塞いで
I just Gimme×Gimme
余計なこと考えていないで
今度は踊りましょう シャバダバダ ドュビドュビドュ
映画のエンドロールみたいに
背の高さとかさねあわせて
酔いもさめないふりをして
いいいから夜が明けてく
足りないくらいがちょうどいい…
なんていじわるばかり言わないで！
まだ足りない これは純愛
好きにさせて
ねえ早く連れていって
微熱にとけちゃいそうな距離で
思考すら奪ってつらぬいてって
その場のしぎ以上の余計なこと言っちゃいそうだな
吐息漏れるその唇で耳を塞いで
この時間も呼吸も止めて
ほてる心の隙間うめて
ここにいる意味をなして
未来なんて iranai
今のあたしを見て！
I just Wanna×Wanna
好きにさせて
ねえ早く連れていって
まつげすら触れちゃいそうな距離で
思考すら奪って探り当てて
その場のしぎ以上の余計なこと言っちゃいそうだな
吐息漏れるその唇をキスで塞いで
鮮やかに彩って
(Forget what I just said)
この世界を照らすような
(Actually, don't forget)
満たす体温最後まで
(Please don't forget… lifetime)
吐息漏れるその唇をキスで塞いで
Don't want to go home, but I have to
Because he comes home. Maybe next time
さあ眠眠打破 昼夜逆転 VOX AC30W
テレキャスター背負ったサブカルボーイがバンド仲間にやっほー
アルバイトはネクラモード タイバンにはATフィールド
“人見知り”宣言で逃げる気か boy
ゆうて お坊っちゃんお嬢ちゃん お金も才能も なまじっかあるだけ厄介でやんす
Boys be ambitious… like this old man
長い前髪 君誰の信者 信者 信者
勘違いすんなよ 教祖はオマエだ
ロキロキのロックンロール かき鳴らすエレクトリックギターは Don't stop! Don't stop!
さあ君の全てを 暴き出してみせろよ
ロキロキのロックンロール さあ 日進月歩
いい曲書いてる？ 動画ふえてる？
「知名度あるけど 人気はそんなにないから 色々大変ですね。」
はっきり言うなよ 匿名アイコン はっきり見せない実生のアイコン
いい歳こいて自意識まだ boy
ぶっかけどんなに 賢くあざとくやったって 10年後にメイクは落ちてんだろ
Boys be ambitious… like this old man
生き抜くためだ キメろ take a “selfy” “selfy” “selfy”
死ぬんじゃねえぞ お互いにな！
ロキロキのロックンロール 薄っぺらいラブソングでもいい Don't stop! Don't stop!
さあ目の前のあの子を 撃ち抜いてみせろよ
ロキロキのロックンロール お茶を濁してちゃ満足できない
スタジオに運ばれたフロアタムとは 安心 不安 心拍数でいっぱい
「実は昨日から 風邪で声が出ません」 は？は？は？は？はあ…
寝言は寝て言え ベイビーベイビーベイビーベイビーベイビーベイビーベイビーベイビー
死ぬんじゃねえぞ お互いにな！！！
ロキロキのロックンロール かき鳴らすエレクトリックギターは Don't stop! Don't stop!
さあ君の全てを 暴き出してみせろよ
ロキロキの ロックンロール
死ぬんじゃねえぞ (死ぬんじゃねえぞ) 死にたくないのは お互い様！
さあ 睡眠打破 昼夜逆転 VOX AC30W
Now, break the sleep, reverse day and night, Vox AC30W
テレキャスター背負った サブカルボーイ
A suburban boy carrying a Telecaster
が バンド仲間にやっほー
saying hello to his bandmates
アルバイトはネクラモード 対バンにはATフィールド
Part-time job in gloomy mode, AT field for joint gigs
“人見知り”宣言で気軽に逃げるか boy
Escaping easily with an "introvert" declaration, boy?
ゆーて お坊っちゃんお嬢ちゃん お金も才能も
I mean, rich kids, you've got money and talent,
なまじっかあるだけ厄介でやんす
but having them half-assedly is just troublesome.
Boys be ambitious... like this old man
長い前髪 君誰の信者
Long bangs, whose believer are you?
信者
Believer,
believer,
勘違いすんなよ 教祖はオマエだ
make no mistake, the guru is you.
ロキロキの rockin' rock' n' roll
Roki-roki's rockin' rock 'n' roll
かき鳴らす electric guitar は don't stop! don't stop!
Strumming the electric guitar, don't stop! don't stop!
さあ 君の全てを 曝け出しちまってみせろよ
Now, show us your everything exposed!
死ぬんじゃねえぞ お互いにな！
Don't you die on me, we're in this together!
ロキロキの rockin' rock' n' roll
Roki-roki's rockin' rock 'n' roll
かき鳴らす electric guitar は don't stop! don't stop!
Strumming the electric guitar, don't stop! don't stop!
さあ 君の全てを 曝け出しちまってみせろよ
Now, show us your everything exposed!
ロキロキの rockin' rock' n' roll
Roki-roki's rockin' rock 'n' roll
死ぬんじゃねえぞ お互いにな！
Don't you die on me, we're in this together!
死にたかねえのは お互様！
Neither of us wants to die!
愛し合う2人 幸せの空
Two people in love under a happy sky
隣同士 あなたとあたし さくらんぼ
Side by side, you and me, sakuranbo
手帳開くとき もう2年たつたんなって
Opening our planner, it's already been two years
やっぱ実感するね なんか照れくさかったりするね
I really feel it, somehow it makes us feel a bit shy
そういや ヒドイコトもされたし ヒドイコトも言ったし
Come to think of it, terrible things were done to me, and I said terrible things too
手を繋ぐとき もっと緊張しちゃって
When holding hands, I get even more nervous
よっぽど意識してんだ ねなんだか照れたりするね
I'm so conscious of it, somehow it makes me feel shy
そういや ヒドイコトもされたし ヒドイコトも言ったし
Come to think of it, terrible things were done to me, and I said terrible things too
瞳がいっぱい詰まった 甘い甘いものです
Packed full of pupils, it's a sweet, sweet thing
泣き泣きの一日や 自転車の旅や
Crying days and bicycle trips
書きあらわせない だって多いんだもん！！
Can't express it all, because there's just so much!!
笑顔咲く 君とつながっていたい
Your smiling face, I want to be connected with you
もしあの向こうに見えるものがあるなら
If there's something visible over there
愛し合う2人 幸せの空
Two people in love under a happy sky
隣同士 あなたとあたし さくらんぼ
Side by side, you and me, sakuranbo
もらったものは そう愛を感じ
What I received is feeling the love
あげたものは もちろん 全力の愛です
What I gave is, of course, love with all my might
やっぱいいものだね 共同作業 罰ゲーム
It's a good thing after all, teamwork and penalty games
思いがけなく歴史は さらに深いけれど
Unexpectedly, our history runs even deeper
1つでも欠けていたら とんでもなく
If even one is missing, it's astonishingly
足りない 足りない 足りない!! 2人の絆
Not enough, not enough, not enough!! Our bond
笑顔咲く 君と抱き合っていたい
Your smiling face, I want to hold you tight
もし遠い未来を 予想するのなら
If we are to predict the distant future
愛し合う2人 いつどの時も
Two people in love, at any and all times
隣同士 あなたとあたし さくらんぼ
Side by side, you and me, sakuranbo
もらったものは そう愛を感じ
What I received is feeling the love
あげたものは もちろん 全力の愛です
What I gave is, of course, love with all my might
やっぱいいものだね 共同作業 罰ゲーム
It's a good thing after all, teamwork and penalty games
思いがけなく歴史は さらに深いけれど
Unexpectedly, our history runs even deeper
1つでも欠けていたら とんでもなく
If even one is missing, it's astonishingly
足りない 足りない 足りない!! 2人の絆
Not enough, not enough, not enough!! Our bond
笑顔咲く 君と抱き合っていたい
Your smiling face, I want to hold you tight
もし遠い未来を 予想するのなら
If we are to predict the distant future
愛し合う2人 いつどの時も
Two people in love, at any and all times
隣同士 あなたとあたし さくらんぼ
Side by side, you and me, sakuranbo
笑顔咲く 君とつながっていたい
Your smiling face, I want to be connected with you
もしあの向こうに見えるものがあるなら
If there's something visible over there
愛し合う2人 幸せの空
Two people in love under a happy sky
隣同士 あなたとあたし さくらんぼ
Side by side, you and me, sakuranbo
もらったものは そう愛を感じ
What I received is feeling the love
あげたものは もちろん 全力の愛です
What I gave is, of course, love with all my might
やっぱいいものだね 共同作業 罰ゲーム
It's a good thing after all, teamwork and penalty games
思いがけなく歴史は さらに深いけれど
Unexpectedly, our history runs even deeper
1つでも欠けていたら とんでもなく
If even one is missing, it's astonishingly
足りない 足りない 足りない!! 2人の絆
Not enough, not enough, not enough!! Our bond
笑顔咲く 君と抱き合っていたい
Your smiling face, I want to hold you tight
もし遠い未来を 予想するのなら
If we are to predict the distant future
愛し合う2人 いつどの時も
Two people in love, at any and all times
隣同士 あなたとあたし さくらんぼ
Side by side, you and me, sakuranbo
もらったものは そう愛を感じ
What I received is feeling the love
あげたものは もちろん 全力の愛です
What I gave is, of course, love with all my might
やっぱいいものだね 共同作業 罰ゲーム
It's a good thing after all, teamwork and penalty games
思いがけなく歴史は さらに深いけれど
Unexpectedly, our history runs even deeper
1つでも欠けていたら とんでもなく
If even one is missing, it's astonishingly
足りない 足りない 足りない!! 2人の絆
Not enough, not enough, not enough!! Our bond
笑顔咲く 君と抱き合っていたい
Your smiling face, I want to hold you tight
もし遠い未来を 予想するのなら
If we are to predict the distant future
愛し合う2人 いつどの時も
Two people in love, at any and all times
隣同士 あなたとあたし さくらんぼ
Side by side, you and me, sakuranbo
笑顔咲く 君とつながっていたい
Your smiling face, I want to be connected with you
もしあの向こうに見えるものがあるなら
If there's something visible over there
愛し合う2人 幸せの空
Two people in love under a happy sky
隣同士 あなたとあたし さくらんぼ
Side by side, you and me, sakuranbo
もういっかい！！
One more time!!
愛し合う2人
You and I, in love,
いつどの時も
anytime,
隣どおし あなたとあたし
side by side, you and I,
あたし さくらんぼ
like cherry blossoms.
パッとパッと晴れやかに 咲かせましょう 花のように
Boom, booming with radiance, let’s bloom it like a flower.
花踊れやいろはにほ
Dance, dance, in the vibrant colors!
欲しいのは 少しの踏み出しからと 弱気な心を開ける魔法のキー
All I want is a small step forward and the magic key to open my timid heart.
勢いよく跳ねて 始まる夢は 本気の夢は
Jumping vigorously, the dream that begins, our true dream,
どんなカチ? 踊れヤ踊れ 散ラサナイデ
what form will it take? Dance, dance! Don't scatter them!
もっともっと一緒に数えたい 新しい景色
I want to count more and more together, a brand-new scenery.
パッとパッと晴れやかに 咲かせましょう 花のように
Boom, booming with radiance, let’s bloom it like a flower.
どんなカタチ?
What form will it take?
散らさないで もっともっと一緒に数えたい
Don't scatter them! I want to count more and more together,
新しい景色
a brand-new scenery.
色は匂へと 散りたくないの
Even though colors bloom and fade, I don't want them to scatter.
咲かせる想いを連ねたなら 乙女とはじまかせたっと
If we string together the feelings we make bloom...
つぶやいてみた
I whispered to myself.
乙女ごころさ
That's a maiden's heart!
迷ってるだけなら何も起こらない
Nothing happens if you just hesitate,
強気で行くんだと瞳で語るよ
my eyes speak of going forward strongly.
そしたらさ「さあ、おいで!」
Then "Come on, now!"
輝く夢の 本気さ夢の 色に変わる
Tomorrow turns into the color of a shining dream.
歌えヤ歌え 揺れながら ずっとずっと一緒に遊びたい 桜色ハーモニー
Sing, sing! While drifting along, I want to play together forever and ever, a cherry blossom-colored harmony.
散りぬるを さっとさっと流れてく
Flowing along with a swish swish, the fleeting scent of flowers,
いつまでも君といたい
I want to be with you forever.
散りぬるを さっとさっと流れてく 出会いと別れに酔いもせず
Flowing along with a swish swish, not getting drunk on meetings and goodbyes,
そっと見つめ合って 君の気配を感じていたい
softly gazing at each other, wanting to feel your presence...
…乙女の願い!
...A maiden's wish!
踊れや 今こんなに嬉しくて
Dance now, I'm so happy!
踊れ ほらこんなに嬉しくて 気分次第で遠くへ飛びそう
Dance, look, I'm so happy, feeling like I could fly far away!
歌えや 今こんなに楽しくて
Sing now, I'm so having fun!
歌え ほらこんなに楽しくて
Sing, look, I'm so having fun!
ずっともっと一緒に遊びたい 気持ちが奏でる 桜色ハーモニー
The feeling of wanting to play together more and more plays a cherry blossom-colored harmony.
色は匂へと パッとパッと 華やかに咲かせましょう 花のように
Boom, booming with radiance, let’s bloom it like a flower.
これからの君が見たい
I want to see what you'll become from now on.
色は匂へと パッとパッと 華やかに 咲かせる想いは連ねたら
Boom, booming with radiance, the feelings we make bloom are timeless...
だって乙女とはじめかさげたっと
After all, whispering that a maiden's path is left to the wind...
つぶやいてみた
I whispered to myself.
乙女ごころさ
That's a maiden's heart!
色は匂へと 散りたくないの
Even though colors bloom and fade, I don't want them to scatter.
散りたくないの
I don't want them to scatter.
ハッピーウェディング前ソング
[Title: Happy Wedding Zen Song]
あれ？なんかちょっといい感じやん？
Huh? Does it feel a bit nice?
君ら相性っちゅう感じやん？
Don't you guys seem to match?
客観的にみてお似合いやん？
Looking at it objectively, aren't you a good match?
趣味とか好きな音楽似てるやん？
Don't your hobbies and favorite music seem similar?
まんざらでもない顔してるやん！
You've got a not-unfavorable look on your face!
あれ？なんかちょっといい感じやん？
Huh? Does it feel a bit nice?
君ら相性っちゅう感じやん？
Don't you guys seem to match?
やっぱり出会いって奇跡やん？
After all, meeting is a miracle, right?
運命とか信じるタイプやろ？
You're the type to believe in fate, aren't you?
ウチが取り持ってあげる！
I'll set you up!
愛とか恋とかそういうのすっ飛ばして
Skipping things like love and romance,
六感で動いてみたらええやん
why don't you try moving on your sixth sense?
ちょっとだけ冷かしてみてもいいかな？
Is it alright if I tease you just a little bit?
キス！キス！キス！キス！キス！キス！キス！
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss! Kiss! Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
からの入籍！入籍！入籍！入籍！入籍！入籍！
And then—Registry! Registry! Registry! Registry! Registry! Registry!
ノリで入籍してみたらええやん
Why don't you try registering your marriage on a whim?
君らお似合いやん それハッピーやん
You guys look good together, that's happy.
二人これから一生ずっと一緒に居ろや速攻
You two should be together forever from now on. Quickly,
婚姻届役所に届けよう
submit the marriage registration to the city office.
入籍してみたらええやん
Try registering your marriage;
後のことは責任取らんけど
I won't take responsibility for what happens afterwards.
きっとうまくいくよ
I'm sure things will go well,
なんとなくそんな気がしてるんだ
I somehow have that feeling.
あれ？なんかちょっといい感じやん？
Huh? Does it feel a bit nice?
もはや君らカップル同然やん！
You're already like a couple!
本格的に考え出してるやん！
You're seriously starting to think about it!
まじで市役所行こうとしてるやん
You're seriously about to go to the city office.
えっ？まじで？
Eh? Seriously?
市役所行こうとしてるやん…
You're about to go to the city office...
大丈夫？まじ大丈夫？？
Are you okay? Are you really okay??
いや、君らがいいならいいんやけどさ
Well, if you guys are fine with it, that's fine, but...
いいの？ほんとにそれで大丈夫？？
Is it okay? Are you really okay with that??
え、ほんとに大丈夫なんな？？？
Eh, are you really okay???????
愛とか恋とかそういうのすっ飛ばして
Skipping things like love and romance,
直感で動いてみたらええやん
why don't you try moving on intuition?
冷静な判断今は捨ててさあ
Throw away calm judgment for now, come on!
キス！キス！キス！キス！キス！キス！キス！
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss! Kiss! Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
からの入籍！入籍！入籍！入籍！入籍！入籍！
And then—Registry! Registry! Registry! Registry! Registry! Registry!
ノリで入籍してみたらええやん
Why don't you try registering your marriage on a whim?
君らお似合いやん それハッピーやん
You guys look good together, that's happy.
二人これから一生ずっと一緒に居ろや速攻
You two should be together forever from now on. Quickly,
ゼクシィ買って式に備えよう
buy Zexy and prepare for the ceremony.
入籍してみたらええやん
Try registering your marriage.
多分2年以内に別れると心のどこかで思っているけど
Although deep in my heart I think you'll break up within two years,
秘密にしておくね
I'll keep it a secret.
金銭感覚ものの価値観からだの相性
Financial sense, values of things, physical compatibility,
言えない過去や消したい過去はお互いにたくさんあるけれど
Unspeakable pasts and pasts you want to erase, you both have plenty,
モラハラ姑問題どうしようもない浮気癖とか不安はあるけどさ…
Moral harassment, mother-in-law problems, helpless cheating habits, anxieties, but...
ノリで入籍してみたらええやん
Why don't you try registering your marriage on a whim?
君らお似合いやん それハッピーやん
You guys look good together, that's happy.
二人これから一生ずっと一緒に居ろや速攻
You two should be together forever from now on. Quickly,
婚姻届役所に届けよう
submit the marriage registration to the city office.
入籍してみたらええやん
Try registering your marriage;
後のことは責任取らんけど
I won't take responsibility for what happens afterwards.
きっとうまくいくよ
I'm sure things will go well,
なんとなくそんな気がしてるんだ
I somehow have that feeling.
入籍してみたらええやん きっと2年以内に別れるけど…
Try registering your marriage, though you'll surely break up within two years...
ノリで入籍してみたらええやん ええやん ええやん ええやん
Why don't you try registering your marriage on a whim? Yeah, yeah, yeah!
おめでとう！！！結婚おめでとう！！！
Congratulations! Congratulations on your wedding!
ハッピーウェディング
Happy Wedding
君が持ってきた漫画
The manga you brought along
くれた知らない名前のお花
And the flower with an unknown name you gave me
今日はまだ来ないかな？
Won't you come over today?
初めての感情知ってしまった
I've come to know an emotion for the very first time
窓に飾った絵画をなぞって ひとり宇宙を旅して
Tracing the painting decorated on the window, traveling through the universe all alone
それだけでいいはずだったのに
It should have been enough with just that, but...
君の手を握ってしまったら
Once I hold your hand,
孤独を知らないこの街にはもう二度と帰ってくることはできないのでしょう
I suppose I'll never be able to return to this town that knows no loneliness
君が手を差し伸べた 光で影が生まれる
A shadow is born from the light where you reached out your hand
歌って聞かせせて この話の続き
Sing and let me hear the rest of this story
連れて行って 見たことない星まで
Take me away to a star I've never seen before
君が持ってきた漫画
The manga you brought along,
くれた知らない名前のお花
the flower with an unfamiliar name you gave me...
今日はまだ来ないかな?
I wonder if it's not time yet?
初めての感情知ってしまった
I've come to know these unprecedented feelings.
窓に飾った絵画をなぞって ひとり宇宙を旅して
Tracing the painting decorated on the window, traveling through space alone,
それだけでいいはずだったのに
even though that should have been enough...
君の手を握ってしまったら
Once I grabbed your hand,
孤独を知らないこの街には
in this town that knows no loneliness,
もう二度と帰ってくることは
returning is no longer possible.
君が手を差し伸べた 光で影が生まれる
You extended your hand, light gives birth to shadow.
歌って聞かせて この話の続き
Sing and let me hear the continuation of this story,
連れて行って 見たことない星まで
take me away to a star I've never seen before.
誰の手も声も届かない 高く聳え立った塔の上へ
To the top of a tower standing high where no one's hand or voice can reach,
飛ばす紙飛行機
launching a paper airplane.
僕は君に笑って欲しいんだ
I want you to smile.
満たされない穴は 惰性の会話や 澄ましいたポーズで
Unfillable voids, inertial conversations, polished poses—
これまでとは埋めてきたけど
up until now we've filled them in, but
退屈な日々を蹴散らして 君と二人で この街中を泳いできたら
if we were to sweep away tedious days and swim through this town together,
それはどれだけ素敵なことでしょう?
how wonderful that would be?
出したことないほど 大きな声でやっと君に伝わる
With a voice so loud I've never used before, it finally reaches you—
歪なくらいさ
distorted irregularity,
世界の端と端を結んで
connecting the ends of the world.
窓に飾った絵画をなぞって ひとり宇宙を旅して
Tracing the painting decorated on the window, traveling through space alone,
それだけでも不自由はないけど
even if it feels restrictive,
僕は選んでみたいの
I want to make my choice.
高鳴る心臓迷いだけの空を 安全なループを今書き換えて
Rewriting safe loops into a sky full of thumping, bewildering heartbeats.
君の手を握ってしまったら
Once I grabbed your hand,
孤独を知らないこの街には
in this town that knows no loneliness,
もう二度と帰ってくることは
returning is no longer possible.
いくらでも迷いながら 光も影も見に行こう
No matter how lost we get, let's go see both light and shadow,
歌って聞かせて この話の続き
sing and let me hear the continuation of this story,
連れて行って 見たことない星まで
take me away to a star I've never seen before.
誰の手も声も届かない 高く聳え立った塔の上へ
To the top of a tower standing high where no one's hand or voice can reach,
飛ばす紙飛行機
launching a paper airplane.
僕は君に笑って欲しいんだ
I want you to smile.
世界の端と端を結んで
Connecting the ends of the world.
壊れていていたのは 世界でしょうか
Was it the world that was broken?
間違っていたのは 世界でしょうか
Was it the world that was mistaken?
あなたには朝がやってこない
Morning never comes for you.
だからあなたの「おはよう」はもう聞けない
That is why I can no longer hear your "good morning."
時が戻ればなんて思いながら
Thinking "If only time could turn back,"
私はあなたをこんな檻に閉じ込めている
I've been locking you inside this narrow cage.
声が枯れるまで歌い続ければ
If I keep singing until my voice grows hoarse,
きっと気が付いてくれるよね
surely you'll notice me, won't you?
またいつか光の降る街を 手を繋いで歩きましょう
Someday, let's walk hand in hand
空の青さを忘れるなんて まったく本当にあなたはお馬鹿ね
forgetting the blueness of the sky—
壊れていたのは世界ではなくて
It wasn't the world that was broken,
間違っていたのはあなただけれど
It was only you who was mistaken.
あなたには朝がやってこない
Morning will never come for you,
だからあなたの「おはよう」はもう聞けない
So I can no longer hear your "Good morning."
嘘で固められた世界でも
Even in a world solidified by lies,
ごめんね あなたに生きていてほしいの
I'm sorry, I want you to keep living.
時が戻れば なんて思いながら
While thinking, "If only time could go back,"
私はもう少しだけ諦めてる
I am giving up just a little bit more.
声が枯れるまで 歌い続けるのはあなただけのためじゃない
The reason I keep singing until my voice is hoarse
isn't just for you alone.
またいつか 春の空を 二人手をつないで 歩きましょう
Someday once again, let's walk hand in hand
through the spring sky.
何も知らない あなたでいいの
It's fine if you don't know anything,
私はどこにも行かないから
Because I won't go anywhere.
「リリィ、リリィ 君の幸せなんて 願っていたあの頃に戻れないんだ」
"Lily, Lily, I can't go back to those days
when I wished for your happiness."
知ってるよ どうにもできないことも でも嫌いになんてなれなかったよ
I know that, I know some things can't be helped,
yet I still couldn't come to hate you.
またいつか 光を歌いながら
Someday once again, while singing of light,
二人手をつないで 歩きましょう
Let's walk hand in hand, the two of us.
明けない夜はないと 教えてくれたこと
Teaching me that there is no night that doesn't end,
私の手を引いてくれたこと
Taking me by the hand,
「あなたを忘れないよ」
"I won't forget you."
「リリィ」「なあに」
"Lily?" "What is it?"
「ねえ ぼくほんとに君が好きだよ」
"Hey, I really, truly love you."
「リリィ」「なあに」「君はどう？」「私も」
"Lily?" "What is it?" "How about you?" "I love you, too."
あなたが好きよ
I love you.
「リリィ」「なあに」
"Lily?" "What is it?"
「ねえ ぼくほんとに君が好きだよ」
"Hey, I really, truly love you."
「リリィ」「なあに」「君はどう？」「私も」
"Lily?" "What is it?" "How about you?" "I love you, too."
小さなかはどういう訳か
It looks like little me, for some reason,
もうすぐここを離れるらしい
is going to depart here soon.
他の仲間より僕が少し
Compared to the others, I was just a little
出来が良かったただ、それだけらしい
better than them. That's all there was.
ただ、僕は褒められることが
I just liked it when you praised me.
誰より臆病だから
Since I was the most timid one,
怒られたくなかったんだ。
I just didn't want you to get mad at me.
世界中の人々と未来のためだと
It was for the entire human race and for our future,
なんか、凄いことを僕に委託するらしい
they're entrusting a huge task to me.
少し、テレるな責任の重い役目だ
This is a little embarrassing, a heavy responsibility...
日毎周りが慌ただしくなる
Things are becoming a little hectic every day.
皆、いつより優しい気がする
Everyone seems nicer to me today.
想ったより小さな箱で 身動き一つできないな
Inside this cramped space, I can't move a muscle.
少し、緊張するけれど 大人しくしているから
I'm a little nervous, but I'll stay still.
「轟音」と「衝撃」秒速8キロの世界
A roaring sound and shock wave, an 8 km/s world!
凄い、怖いよ！何が起こってるっていうんだ！
This is really scary! What's going on?!
そしてまた、戻ってきて褒められるんだ。
And when I come back, everyone's going to praise me.
いいでしょう？ねえ……。
That's okay, right? Hey...?
僕なんかいなくても
Even if I weren't here,
君は春のように優しかった
you were as gentle as spring.
それはきっと今頃気づいた
Only now did I realize that.
夢の中で君に出会えたならなんて
If only I could meet you in my dreams...
アイミスユー このままいってしまえたらなんて
I miss you... If I could just go on like this,
青春を春を連れ去ってしまえば
taking away youth and spring...
アイラブユー このままいってしまえたら 僕は泣いている君を
I love you... If I could just go on like this, you who are crying,
傷つけてしまった今わかってるよ
I hurt you—now I understand.
アイミスユー このままいってしまえたらなんて
I miss you... If I could just go on like this,
冴えてる僕は君を許してけなくて
clearsighted me couldn't forgive you.
アイラブユー このままいってしまえたら僕は最愛の君に愛を
I love you... If I could just go on like this, my love to my dearest
伝えられたなら
if I could have conveyed it...
さよならさ
farewell.
はい、というわけでここまで見てくれてありがとう！
Yes, so thank you so much for watching up to here!
最後の曲と重大発表が まだ実は残ってるんですが
There's actually still the final song and a major announcement left,
その前に グッズのご案内を先にしたいと思います！
but before that, I'd like to introduce the merchandise first!
てってれーん！ 紫咲シオン活動5周年記念グッズ！ イェーイ！
Tada! Murasaki Shion 5th Anniversary merchandise! Yay!
ということで 活動記念5周年フルセットはこんな感じになっています。
So, the 5th Anniversary Full Set looks like this.
1個ずつ 丁寧 に紹介していくので最後まで見てってください。
I'll be introducing each item carefully, so please watch till the end.
というわけでですね、まず フルセット購入特典なんですけど、え、まずここがもうメインというか、もうでっかい、もうでっかい所なんですけど
So first, about the full set purchase bonus... This is the main part, a really, really big deal, but...
なんと 今回なんですけど これ 多分 最初で最後レベルだと思います。今回 フルセット 購入した方全員に 直筆サイン入り チェキ風ブロマイドカードがついてきます！
Amazingly, this time—I think this is a once-in-a-lifetime level—everyone who purchases the full set will get a hand-signed Instax-style card!
直筆サイン入りです、全部。
It's hand-signed, every single one.
数量限定じゃないのは 多分なんですけど 最初で最後かなって 思います。この戦争を俺が止めに来た。
It's probably not limited in quantity, but I think it's the first and last time. "I have come to stop this war."
というわけで、あの 是非 あのフルセットで購入したら 直筆サイン入りチェキ風カードがついてくるので、そちらも あの 数量限定じゃないから あの 慌てないでください。
So please make sure that if you buy the full set, you get the hand-signed card, so don't panic since it's not quantity-limited!
というわけでですね やっと グッズを あの1つ目をちゃんと紹介していきたいと思います。
So, let's finally properly introduce the first piece of merchandise.
まず 1つ目！ キラキラ⭐︎2層アクリルパネル！
First up! Sparkling 2-Layer Acrylic Panel!
ということでキラキラ星2層アクリルパネル。
So, the sparkling star 2-layer acrylic panel.
なんと キラキラしちゃっている あの 層になってる アクリルパネルですね めっちゃ可愛いイラストをね あのアメもち先生に描いてもらいました。
Amazingly, it's an acrylic panel with sparkling layers! We had Ame-mochi-sensei draw a super cute illustration for it.
めっちゃかわいいです あの塩っこがね 順調なしゅし掴んで えしおんがゲームしてる感じですね めっちゃかわいいよねこれ 本当に お部屋にね あのぜひ飾ってほしいなって
It's super cute! Shio-ko grabbing a shushi... Shion playing a game. It's so cute, really. I'd really love for you to display it in your room.
今までね アクリルパネルとか そういうものは あの出したことがなかったので 今回はですね アクリルパネルにしてみました キラキラしててとってもかわいいです
Up until now, I haven't released things like acrylic panels, so this time I decided to make it an acrylic panel. It's sparkly and super cute.
というわけで 次！ 激カワタンブラー！
So, next! Super Cute Tumbler!
はい こちら皆んな 欲しいなって 思ってましたよね うん 絶対思ってたはず もう絶対的に思ってた
Yes, everyone wanted this, right? Yep, you definitely did. You definitely thought so.
タンブラー欲しい！ 最近タンブラー欲しかったんだよねって 思ってた しおんも思ってた
I want a tumbler! I've been wanting a tumbler recently, I thought. Shion thought so too.
いや タンブラー欲しいなって 思ってて これ めっちゃかわいくて めっちゃこだわって作ったんですよ。
I thought, "I want a tumbler," and I made this super cute, with a lot of attention to detail.
そもそも あの中身が見える透明な蓋 って書いてあって あのそう中身が見えるんですね上から で 蓋がシリコンになってて ピンク色のシリコンになってて で 外身 が あのピンクと薄紫のパステルカラーのグラデーションになってて
First of all, it says "transparent lid where you can see the contents"—so you can see inside from the top! And the lid is pink silicone. And the outer body is a pastel color gradient of pink and light purple.
で このデザインが なんて言うんだろな ちょっとぷっくしたプリントになってて こう指で触ると なんかちょっとだけあのぷこってしてる感じ 本当に もうちょっともうあの1ミリとかもないレベルのぷこって感じの
And the design is... how should I say? It has a slightly raised print. When you touch it with your finger, it feels just a little bit popped out—really, less than a millimeter of a raised feel.
を身に付けてます。
Hi, I'm wearing...
アン ドゥ トロワ
One, two, three.
Ah...
高らかに
Proudly...
「所詮は」だなんて 分かったふりして 口から出まかせで
Acting like you know it's "just the way things are,"
「ホントは」だなんて 甘すぎ？軽侮痴、言いたくないんだって
"The truth is..." Is that too naive? I hate saying stuff like that!
ノイズ無視して 全部笑い飛ばして
Ignoring the noise, laughing everything off,
不安拭って 立ち止まるな
Wiping away the anxiety, don't stop in your tracks.
そらさないで 強くいさせて アン・ドゥ・トロワ
Don't look away, let me stay strong, un, deux, trois.
０時を回っても 逃げずに戦っているの
Even past midnight, I keep fighting without running away.
気高く華麗に 舞い上がる
Soaring high, noble and graceful.
泣いてる暇なんかない
There's no time to be crying.
「タラレバ」なんかじゃなく「これから」を生きたいの
Instead of "what-ifs," I want to live in the "from now on."
反撃開始のドレスを着て
Wearing the dress to start our counterattack,
魔法解ける前に
Before the magic wears off...
さあ ご覧あれ 君のシンデレラ アン・ドゥ・トロワ
Now behold, your Cinderella, un, deux, trois.
ガラスの靴履いて 可愛く映ってますか？
Wearing glass slippers, do I look cute?
誇らしげに 踊って見せよう
Let me show you how proudly I can dance.
これが 私なんだ
This is who I am.
Shall We Dance!
Ah...
誇らしげに 踊って見せよう
Let me show you how proudly I can dance.
もっと Shall We Dance ねぇ？
More, shall we dance, right?
あっ、ちょっと待って！
Ah, wait a second!
このあと24時から、オリジナル曲
Starting at 24:00 tonight,
「シンデレラ・マジック」の配信が始まるからみんなチェックしてね！
the streaming of "Cinderella Magic" begins, so make sure to check it out!